[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Crocodiles like to stay motionless in water and wait for the perfect time to strike. These powerful prehistoric creatures annually give what estimated number of fatalities?", "correct_answer": "600-800", "incorrect_answers": ["1000-1500", "50-100", "100-200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this US state means flat water and is derived from the name of the Platte River that flows through the state.", "correct_answer": "Nebraska", "incorrect_answers": ["Montana", "Utah", "Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This nut, used in a number of cola drinks both for its aroma and refreshing qualities, contains caffeine, which explains its energizing effect.", "correct_answer": "Kola nut", "incorrect_answers": ["Hazelnut", "Peanut", "Chestnut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the motion picture, Thunderball, she befriends James Bond and puts him on the trail of  the villain, who happens to be her guardian.", "correct_answer": "Domino Derval", "incorrect_answers": ["Amelia Abbott", "Charlotte Corday", "Ginette Gibson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Radiohead song did Christopher Nolan want to use in Memento, but couldnt due to insufficient budget?", "correct_answer": "Paranoid Android", "incorrect_answers": ["Kid A", "Karma Polcie", "Fake Plastic Trees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This stealth aircraft was used during Operation Desert Storm in 1991.", "correct_answer": "F-117 Nighthawk", "incorrect_answers": ["F-22 Raptor", "Joint Strike Fighter", "FA/18 Super Hornet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Filipino word maganda means beautiful in English.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of the six brothers Carlo, Bindo, Alfieri, Mario, Ettore and Ernesto, who were all involved with automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Maserati", "incorrect_answers": ["Lamborghini", "Lancia", "Ferrari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is King Harold, Fionas father in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Bear", "Fox", "Chameleon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This British car make was founded under the name Swallow Sidecar Company in 1922, and is known for its elegant sports cars and luxury saloons.", "correct_answer": "Jaguar", "incorrect_answers": ["Bentley", "Rolls-Royce", "Land Rover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first host of the popular late-night show Saturday Night (later called Saturday Night Live)?", "correct_answer": "George Carlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Martin", "Richard Pryor", "John Goodman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturated fats have proven to be the main dietary cause of high blood LDL cholesterol levels.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]